Guide to the T. W. Anderson Papers SC0911
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-093
  - Research Files
    - Student volume 3 number 2 incorporating data statistics, 1999 Nov (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Student volume 3 number 2 incorporating data statistics, 1999 Nov (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Leather, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Psychometrika journal Volume 63 Number 1, 1998 Mar (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Vinod, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Vinod, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Velu, 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - unlabeled, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - unlabeled (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - A Note on the distribution of a rating - TWA, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Lecture, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - work for talk (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Misc., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - unlabeled, 1989 Dec (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Anova, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Percentage Points (tables), 1989 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Dist. Of LRC, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Santa Barbara Conference, 1989 Nov 18 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - New paper, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - To TWA from Yasuo, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Yasuo, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Dist. Of Ch. Notes + vectors, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - unlabeled, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - 40. Ethics and randomized studies, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Evaluation of the Expedied valued a determinanant (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Wold paper, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Neil Henry Dissertation, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - LIMLK (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - LIMLK (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Sams Discussion - tables, etc, 1976 April (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - TSLS, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - unlabeled (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - 1975 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - LIMLK paper, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - unlabeled (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - unlabeled (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Soura (LIMLK TR), 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Saura, 1976 June (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - MA Goodness of Fil (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - unlabeled (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - unlabeled, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - notes (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Mathematical Reviews of the Research Papers of T. W. Anderson (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - References for the Second Edition of T. W. Anderson's An Introduction to Multivariate Statistical Analysis Reviews (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence on 2nd Edition (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - transparencies for Santa Barbara (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Anderson: invariant measures, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - TSA. Instructor's manual. New data App. A (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - TSA Enata, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - III Discussion and, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - VI Additional TSA discussion (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Manual, TSA (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - LIML Expansion: Root (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Paper 93 on the structure, 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - paper no. 102, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Figures for Congress paper. Paper 102 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Paper no. 103, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Paper 103, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Paper no. 104 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Paper no. 104, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Paper no. 105 comparison, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - 116. Multivariate linear relations (1), 1987 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - 116 Multivariate relations (2), 1987 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Par. Consistency papers 117, 141, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Consistency, Parameter, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Perlman -M.A., 1978 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Perlman II, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - 141, Parameter consistency proofs, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Paper #130, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Frisch, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Perlman, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Haavelmo References, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Haavelmo clippings, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Haavelmo bio + Biblior, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Haavelmo: papers about, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Haavelmo: notes, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Haavelmo's own papers, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - 135, (Fang) Theory and appreciation of elliptically, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Non-normal foils in lecture #140, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - nonnormal: notes #140, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Nonnormal: MS #140, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - nonnormal: proofs, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Inference in linear models, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Inference in linear models, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Inference in linear models (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Review of Fuller, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - 144 Asympt. Robustness (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - unlabeled (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - correspondence, 1990 Jun-July (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Stat 204, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Asymptote TWA + K, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - unlabeled (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - papers, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - PC - Old notes (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - M15.1 Classification: Asympt. Expansion, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - M15.2 Classification: Asymp. Expansion, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - M15.3 Classification: Asymp. Exp., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - R12.1 Atl. Change - Ch 2, 3, 4 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - R12.2 Atl. Change Ch 5, 6, 7, 8 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - R12.3 Alt. change - other models (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - R12.4 Alt. change - data, 1940-1948 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - R12.5 Atl. Change - for revision (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - R12.6 Alt. change - revision of short version (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - R12.8 Att change - long version (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - R12.10 Altitude Change - AMS (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - R12.11 Altitude Change, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - R13.1 Kellogg Paper - computation notes (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - R13.2 Kellogg Paper - drafts, coresp., 1954 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - R14.1 Corver Pb. - paper (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - R14.2 Couver Pb - notes (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - R17 birshick note, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - R20.1 Lt Pr in 7a mannuscripts (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - St. Pr. In 7a - talks R20.2, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - St. Pr. In F. A. - old notes R20.3, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - St. Pr. In 7a Sec. 3 simplex R20.4 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - R20.5 St. Pr. In 7A Sec 4.1 circular markov process (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - R20.6 St. Pr in 7A Sec 4.2 Polar markov processes (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - St. Pr in FA - Sec 5 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - R20.8 St. Pr in 7A misc notes (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - R20.9 St. Pr in 7A Relab + Watson (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Work in April (P. C.) old notes (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - PC old notes (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - M5 MLE when observations are missing, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - M6 MLE when observations are missing (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - M6 MLE when observations are missing (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - M7 Evaluation of the Cummulations with F. Lord, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Classification (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - M8.1 Classification (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Classification - notes (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - M8.2 Classification II (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Classification project, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Classification (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Classification project, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - M8.3 Discriminant functions (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - notes on "the choice of…", 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Notes on Author Cohen (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Misc. on Pb (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - IBM: Selection of Variates in regression (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - On the distribution of the .., 1954 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - On the distribution of the two-sample (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - On the distribution of the two-sample, 1961 April (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Two-sample, 1961 July (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - two-sample numerical work, 1961 Fall-Winter (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - R.15 Sequential Analysis (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Sec 5 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Sec 3 (-5) (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Recent, 1961 Sep (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Notes on Choice of Ob. Paper (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Current Review, 1992 Nov 8 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Tyler (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Papers + talks, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Talks, abstract, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Talks, 1998 Oct (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - unlabeled, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Nathan (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - R18.1 SA Old mins (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - R18.2 SA, 1957 Oct- Nov (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - R18.3 SA, 1958 Apr (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - 18.4 SA 2 integrals (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - R18.5 normal approx, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - 18.6 Optimal procedures (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - R18.7 SA notes on revision (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - R18.8 notes (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - R18.9 SA notes on K-W (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - R18.10 min by analysis (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - R18.11 SA recent notes (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - R18.12 misc SA (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - R18.13 SA misc (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - R18.14 SA misc (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - R18.15 SA talks (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - R18.16 SA sect. 4 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - R18.17 SA 4.4 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - R18.18 SA 4.4 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - R18.19 SA Sec 5 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - R18.20 SA original summary (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - R18.21 SA sec 5 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - R18.22 SA Accuracy of Comp. (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - R18.23 SA Accuracy of Comp (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - R18.24 Computation formulas (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - R18.25 SA Computation misc (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - R18.26 computation formulas (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - R18.27 computations at A=.95 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - R18.28 computation at .9453 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - R18.29 SA Bump's computing (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - R18.30 summary of computation (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - R18.31 numerical results (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - R18.32 computations (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - R18.34 computation of mill's ratio (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - R.18.35 tables of Mill's ratio (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - R18.36 on computation (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - R18.37 paper + notes on future work, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - R18.38 Appendix (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - R18.39 recent/misc SA, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - R19.1 Optimum property of … notes, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - R19.2 Optimum Property of SPRT manuscripts (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - R19.3 Unique… of SPRT (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - R23 comments on F + of multiple TS, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - tests of linear hypothesis, 1962-1963 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Tests of covariance matrices, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - M14.1 randomness of directions correspondence (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - M14.2 Randomness of directions (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - M14.3 randomness of directions: correspondence with Stephen, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - MIT covariance matrices with L mean structure: asymptotically efficient estimation, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - FinaL WITH a PC paper (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - notes on PC, 1960-1961 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Principal components (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - M3 principal components (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - multivariate nonparameter, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Sampling parameter I (Box 26, Folder 54)